prntly.com 2017-05-25

# Privacy Policy - We keep you safe, unlike anywhere else | Prntly

Sponsored Links: 

Your privacy is very important to us. At Prntly we have a few fundamental principles that we follow:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our site.

Prntly LLC (“Prntly”) operates several websites including Prntly.com. It is Prntly’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Prntly collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Prntly’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Prntly’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Prntly may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Prntly also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blogs. Prntly only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Prntly’s websites choose to interact with Prntly in ways that require Prntly to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Prntly gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment on our blog to provide a username and email address. Those who wish to receive Prntly updates via email, we collect their emails. In each case, Prntly collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Prntly. Prntly does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Prntly uses cookies to help Prntly  identify and track visitors, their usage of Prntly website, and their website access preferences. Prntly visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Prntlys websites, with the drawback that certain features of Prntly’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Prntly, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Prntly goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Prntly may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Prntly and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Prntly may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Prntly’s sole discretion. Prntly encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
